

CONTACT 🔀



Wa: 087832171593 email: ayuwidya5601@gmail.com LinkedIn: Ayu Widya Inggit Github: ayuwidyainggit Gitlab: ayuwidyainggit

SKILL



HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, ReactJS, Javascript

MY PROJECT



Landing Page Coffeeshop https://ayuwidyainggit.github. io/WebsiteCoffeshop/

Website Ecommerce https://ayuwidyainggit.github. io/Website-ecommerce/

Landing Page Saasup https://ayuwidyainggit.github. io/frontend-mysaas/

POS - (React Redux): https://ayuwidyainggit.github. io/POS---React-Redux/

AYU WIDYA INGGIT

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Ayu Widya Inggit and I have the ability to quickly adapt to different environments and cultures. With my experience in building web applications using React JS, I am confident in my ability to contribute to any team and make an immediate impact.



EDUCATION

STMIK AKAKOM YOGYAKARTA

2016 - 2019 D3 - Computerized Accounting



EXPERIENCE

PT INFOSYS SOLUSI TERPADU **Business Analyst (February 2022 - now)**

- Communicate with clients about the product to be built / developed
- Communicate with teams about the product to be built / developed
- Creating flowcharts, use case diagram, sequence diagram
- Create FSD

PT MEDIKA DIGITAL NUSANTARA System Analyst (Mei 2020 - Feb 2022)

- Communicate with clients about the product to be built / developed
- Create documentation for developers according to client wishes
- Create database design, query MySQL, Oracle
- Create a system design and Mockup
- API design
- Creating flowcharts, table relations, diagrams
- Manual testing and data validation

KREASI KODE

System Analyst (Nov 2019 - Mei 2020)

- Create planning, design system, and document for client and document for developer
- Create mockup, flowchart, database design, query, triggerm and procedure
- Manual Testing and Data Validation